A Guide to the Fries Textile Plant Records, 1900-1988
Special Collections, Virginia Tech
- Series I: Company Files, 1908-1979
  - Markwell Mfg. Co., Inc., October- November 1941 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Maryland Casualty Company, 1941 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Merchants Notion Company, February- November 1941 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Mason and Dixon Truck Lines, September- November 1941 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - H. Metzger's Sons, Inc., August- October 1941 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Mine Safety Appliance Co., November 1941 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Monarch Elevator Company, January- February 1941 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Morton Mfg. Company, February- December 1941 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Morse Twist Drill and Machine Co., November 1941 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Mueller Company, May- December 1941 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - T. J. Murphy Fur Co., February 1941 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Miscellaneous "N", March- December 1941 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Nachman Spring-Filled Corp., February- March 1941 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - National Cotton Council of America, July 1941 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - National Starch Products, January- May 1941 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Newark Wire Cloth Company, June- August 1941 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - N and W Railway Co., February- December 1941 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - The Norlander Machine Co., August 1941 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - North Carolina Finishing Co., February 1941 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - The North Electric Mfg. Co., January- April 1941 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Miscellaneous "O", July- September 1941 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Odell Mill Supply Co., 1941 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Miscellaneous "P", February- December 1941 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Parks and Woolson Machine Co., February- April 1941 (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - Pease Woodwork Co., February- March 1941 (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Peck, Stow and Wilcox Co., March- April 1941 (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - Penick and Ford, Ltd., January- May 1941 (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - Pittsburgh Equitable Meter Co., March- October 1941 (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - Pittsburgh Plate Glass Co., February- November 1941 (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - Pless Elec. and Mfg. Company, March- June 1941 (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - Postmaster, Fries, VA (See also- Geo K. Fielder), August- September 1941 (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - Priorities, August- December 1941 (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - Protective Life Insurance Co., January- June 1941 (Box 155, Folder 6)
  - Pyrene Mfg. Co., March- May 1941 (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - Miscellaneous "Q", October 1941 (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - Quaker S.S. Line, January- February 1941 (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - Miscellaneous "R", March- November 1941 (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - Railway Supply and Mfg. Co., January- August 1941 (Box 7, Folder 64)
  - Ransome Concrete Machinery Co., January- March 1941 (Box 7, Folder 65)
  - Reliance Steel Corporation (Sheet Metal Mfg. Div.), January 1941 (Box 7, Folder 66)
  - J. E. Rhoads and Sons, January- October 1941 (Box 7, Folder 67)
  - Federal Reserve Bank of Richmond, September- October 1941 (Box 7, Folder 68)
  - Riverside Mills, 1941 (Box 7, Folder 69)
  - Roanoke Hardware Co., January 1941 (Box 7, Folder 70)
  - Roanoke-Webster Brick Co., Inc., July- September 1941 (Box 7, Folder 71)
  - Rock Hill Ptg. and Fin. Co., January- October 1941 (Box 7, Folder 72)
  - H. B. Rogers, Inc., January- July 1941 (Box 7, Folder 73)
  - David Rothschild Company, January- May 1941 (Box 7, Folder 74)
  - Roxboro Cotton Mills, April- May 1941 (Box 7, Folder 75)
  - Joseph T. Ryerson and Son, Inc., March- October 1941 (Box 7, Folder 76)
  - Miscellaneous "S", 1941 (Box 7, Folder 77)
  - Geo. Sachsenmaier Co., January- September 1941 (Box 7, Folder 78)
  - Saco-Lowell Shops, January- June 1941 (Box 7, Folder 79)
  - J. W. Scott and Company, January- September 1941 (Box 7, Folder 80)
  - Seaboard Airline Railway, July- November 1941 (Box 7, Folder 81)
  - Service Appliance Co, Inc., April- December 1941 (Box 7, Folder 82)
  - James W. Seville, April- October 1941 (Box 7, Folder 83)
  - Sheet Metal Mfg. Division (Steel Heddle Mfg. Co.), March- October 1941 (Box 7, Folder 84)
  - Signode Steel Strapping Co., August- September 1941 (Box 7, Folder 85)
  - Singer Sewing Machine Co., January- February 1941 (Box 7, Folder 86)
  - The Skyebryte Co., July- August 1941 (Box 7, Folder 87)
  - Mr. L.P. Smith, September- October 1941 (Box 7, Folder 88)
  - E. E. Smith and Son, July- November 1941 (Box 7, Folder 89)
  - Gordon Smith and Company, July- October 1941 (Box 7, Folder 90)
  - S. Morgan Smith Co., July- October 1941 (Box 7, Folder 91)
  - Smith-Courtney Company, April- August 1941 (Box 7, Folder 92)
  - Socony-Vacuum Oil Co., January- September 1941 (Box 7, Folder 93)
  - Social Security Board, 1941 (Box 155, Folder 7)
    This material is restricted for 75 yers due to personally identifiable information. Contact Special Collections for additional information.
  - Sonoco Products Company, February- September 1941 (Box 7, Folder 95)
  - Southern Bleachery, October- November 1941 (Box 7, Folder 96)
  - Southern Converting Co., 1941 (Box 7, Folder 97)
  - Southern Electric Service Co., June- November 1941 (Box 7, Folder 98)
  - Southern Nail Co., March- September 1941 (Box 7, Folder 99)
  - Southern Oxygen Co., May- December 1941 (Box 7, Folder 100)
  - Southern Shuttles, Inc., January- November 1941 (Box 7, Folder 101)
  - Southern Spindle and Flyer Co., August 1941 (Box 7, Folder 102)
  - Southern Standard Mill Supply Co., March- June 1941 (Box 7, Folder 103)
  - Southern Steamship Company, January 1941 (Box 7, Folder 104)
  - The Spencer Turbine Co., May 1941 (Box 7, Folder 105)
  - Spring Cotton Company, July- October 1941 (Box 7, Folder 106)
  - A. E. Staley Mfg. Co., August- September 1941 (Box 7, Folder 107)
  - Standard Oil Company, 1941 (Box 7, Folder 108)
  - Stein, Hall and Company, Inc., 1941 (Box 7, Folder 109)
  - Sugar Beet Products Co., January- November 1941 (Box 7, Folder 110)
  - Sullivan Machinery Company, July- November 1941 (Box 7, Folder 111)
  - Superior Sterling Company, 1941 (Box 7, Folder 112)
  - Swift and Company, May- November 1941 (Box 7, Folder 113)
  - Miscellaneous T, February- December 1941 (Box 7, Folder 114)
  - Taylor Instrument Companies, March- December 1941 (Box 7, Folder 115)
  - Terrell Machine Company, April- December 1941 (Box 7, Folder 116)
  - Textile Mill Suply Co., 1941 (Box 7, Folder 117)
  - Textile Salvage Company, June- July 1941 (Box 7, Folder 118)
  - P. N. Thorpe and Company, April- June 1941 (Box 7, Folder 119)
  - Tidewater Supply Company, January- November 1941 (Box 7, Folder 120)
  - The Tildesley Coal Company, March- November 1941 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Traffic Department (folder 1 of 3), January- March 1941 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Traffic Department (folder 2 of 3), April- May 1941 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Traffic Department (folder 3 of 3), June- December 1941 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Town of Fries, April 8, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Trinacria Specialty Mfg. Co., March- May 1941 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous "U", April- December 1941 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - United Fruit Company, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Federal Power Commission U. S. Government, March- May 1941 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - U. S. Government (folder 1 of 2), 1941 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - U. S. Government (folder 2 of 2), 1941 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - U. S. Ring Traveler Company, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - C. L. Upchurch and Sons, Inc., 1941 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Miscellaneous "V", December 1940- October 1941 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Miscellaneous "M", 1943 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Metallizing Co. of America, May- October 1943 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Mente and Co. Inc., December 1942- November 1943 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Mill Power Supply Co., January- June 1943 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - The Morris Malinow Co., March 1943 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - The Morton Method, March- July 1943 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Maryland Casualty Co., January- October 1943 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Miscellaneous "N", December 1942- December 1943 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Nashville Bag and Burlap Co., April 1943 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - National Cotton Council of America, February- October 1943 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - North Electric Mfg. Co., February- December 1943 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - State of North Carolina, April- July 1943 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Norfolk and Western, January- November 1943 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Miscellaneous "O", May- December 1943 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Odell Mill Supply Co. (folder 1 of 2), December- August 1943 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Odell Mill Supply Co. (folder 2 of 2), January- July 1943 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - The Oster Manufacturing Co., April- May 1943 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - J. H. McAden Inc., December 1942- August 1943 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Miscellaneous "P", 1943 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Parke, Davis and Co., April- November 1943 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Pless Electric Co., April 1943 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Pyrene Manufacturing Co., March- August 1943 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Ray Pressure Snubber Co., January- February 1943 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - R and C Cotton Co., February- August 1943 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Arthur Reid, April- October 1943 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Rigler Engineering Co., June- September 1943 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Riverside Mills, 1943 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - David Rothschild Company, 1943 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Miscellaneous "R", December 1942- December 1943 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Miscellaneous "S", 1943 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Saco-Lowell Shops, January- June 1943 (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - St. Louis Button Co., March- April 1943 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Salem Steel Company, March- June 1943 (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Service Appliance Co., January- October 1943 (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - P. Shore Shipping Co., 1943 (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - Singer Sewing Machine Co., January- September 1943 (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - S.K.F. Industries, Inc., March- December 1943 (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - Socony-Vacuum Oil Co., January- February 1943 (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - Social Security Board (folder 1 of 2), January- May 1943 (Box 155, Folder 8)
  - Social Security Board (folder 2 of 2), June- December 1943 (Box 155, Folder 9)
  - Sonoco Products Co., January- February 1943 (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - United States Gov't. (folder 1 of 2), 1943 (Box 8, Folder 56)
  - United States Gov't. (folder 2 of 2), 1943 (Box 8, Folder 57)
  - South-Eastern Underwriters Association (Box 8, Folder 58)
  - Southern Electric Service Co., Inc., March- April 1943 (Box 8, Folder 59)
  - Southern Oxygen Co., February 1943- November 1944 (Box 8, Folder 60)
  - Southern Pacific Lines, February- November 1943 (Box 8, Folder 61)
  - Southern Standard Mill Supply, August- December 1943 (Box 8, Folder 62)
  - Spaugh Paper Co., February- September 1943 (Box 8, Folder 63)
  - Standard Oil Company, October 1942- December 1943 (Box 8, Folder 64)
  - Steel Heddle Mfg. Co. (See also Southern Shuttle), January 1943- August 1944 (Box 8, Folder 65)
  - Superior Sterling Co., 1943 (Box 8, Folder 66)
  - Textile Mill Supply Co., 1943 (Box 8, Folder 67)
  - W. G. Theobald, May- June 1943 (Box 8, Folder 68)
  - The Tildesley Coal Company, 1943 (Box 8, Folder 69)
  - Traffic Department (folder 1 of 3), December 1942- April 1943 (Box 8, Folder 70)
  - Traffic Department (folder 2 of 3), May- August 1943 (Box 8, Folder 71)
  - Traffic Department (folder 3 of 3), September- December 1943 (Box 8, Folder 72)
  - Miscellaneous "T", February- December 1943 (Box 8, Folder 73)
  - Taylor Instrument Companies, January- November 1943 (Box 8, Folder 74)
  - Terrell Machine Co., July- November 1943 (Box 8, Folder 75)
  - Trinacria Specialty Co., July- September 1943 (Box 8, Folder 76)
  - U.S. Office of Defense Transportation, April- December 1943 (Box 8, Folder 77)
  - Wage and Hour Division, April- October 1943 (Box 8, Folder 78)
  - U.S. War Commission Employment Service for Virginia, May- September 1943 (Box 8, Folder 79)
  - U. S. Ring Traveler Co., March- October 1943 (Box 8, Folder 80)
  - C. L. Upchurch and Sons, Inc., March- December 1943 (Box 8, Folder 81)
  - Miscellaneous "U", January- June 1943 (Box 8, Folder 82)
  - (U.S.) Army and Navy (folder 1 of 2), January- February 1943 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - (U.S.) Army and Navy (folder 2 of 2), March- December 1943 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - U. S. Priorities, June 1942- October 1943 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - U. S. Boys in Military Service, 1943 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous "V", January- October 1943 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Virginia-Carolina Chemical Co., July- August 1943 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Commonwealth of Virginia, October 1942- March 1944 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Virginia Mfgr's Association, February- December 1943 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - O.C.D. Virginia Telephone 3442-1, February- November 1943 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Va. Unemployment Compensation Commission, April- December 1943 (Box 155, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous "W", January- October 1943 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Waltham Watch Co., February- May 1943 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - War Eagle Coal Sales Co., 1943 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Washington Mills Co. Mayodan, March- November 1943 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Western Maine Express, 1943 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Westinghouse Mfg. Co., March- November 1943 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Troy Whitehead Machinery Co., March- November 1943 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Whitin Machine Works, February- December 1943 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - WPB (folder 1 of 2), 1943 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - WPB (folder 2 of 2), 1943 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Miscellaneous "Y", 1943 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Miscellaneous "Z", May 25, 1943 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - McAlister, John W. Jr., April 1947 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Miscellaneous "M", 1947 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Chas. McCrea (See Leckie Coal Co.), February- November 1947 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Booker McClay, February- June 1947 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - McDowell Associates, Inc., February- March 1947 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - J B McCreary Co. Inc, August- December 1947 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - James McGraw, Inc., January- March 1947 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - M.B Mfg. Co., April- May 1947 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Magnetrol, Inc, March- September 1947 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Johns Manville, January- October 1947 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Walter Maguire Co. Inc., August 1947 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Marion Cinder Block, February- September 1947 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Master Builders, August 1947 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Marquette Metal Products Co., 1947 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Maryland Casualty Co., 1947 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - S E Massengill Co, August- September 1947 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Jas. H Matthews and Co, August- September 1947 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Medley Mfg. Co., February- August 1947 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Mill Power Supply Co., February- December 1947 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Monroe Calculating Machine Co., 1947 (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Henry M Moore, September 1947 (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Morton Suggestion System, March- December 1947 (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Mtn City Foundry and Machine, March- August 1947 (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Mt. Hope Machinery Co., January- August 1947 (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Miscellaneous N, January- July 1947 (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - National Electric Coil Co., January- August 1947 (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - National Foreman's Institute, April 1947 (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - Natural Slate Blackboard Co, July- December 1947 (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - Neuss, Hasslein and Co, Inc., January 1947 (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - Newlin Hardware Co., April- September 1947 (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - Niagara Alkali Company, June- December 1947 (Box 9, Folder 53)
  - Noland Company, June- November 1947 (Box 9, Folder 54)
  - Norfolk and Western Railway Co., 1947 (Box 9, Folder 55)
  - North Electric Mfg. Co., February 1947 (Box 9, Folder 56)
  - Northup and O'Brien, February- May 1947 (Box 9, Folder 57)
  - Numo Machine and Engineering Co, October- December 1947 (Box 9, Folder 58)
  - Miscellaneous O, March- April 1947 (Box 9, Folder 59)
  - Odell Mill Supply Co., 1947 (Box 9, Folder 60)
  - D W Onan and Sons Inc., May 1947 (Box 9, Folder 61)
  - Miscellaneous P, January- September 1947 (Box 9, Folder 62)
  - J C Paddock Co., May 1947 (Box 9, Folder 63)
  - Parke, Davis Co., May- September 1947 (Box 9, Folder 64)
  - Parks Cramer Co, May- October 1947 (Box 9, Folder 65)
  - Patterson Bag Co., May- June 1947 (Box 9, Folder 66)
  - Pension Service Co, September 24, 1947 (Box 9, Folder 67)
  - Piedmont Mountain Freight, January- November 1947 (Box 9, Folder 68)
  - Phillips-Davis Inc., February- December 1947 (Box 9, Folder 69)
  - Port of New Orleans, January 13, 1947 (Box 9, Folder 70)
  - Platnick Bros, April- May 1947 (Box 9, Folder 71)
  - Porst Bros. Mfg. Co., April- June 1947 (Box 9, Folder 72)
  - Power Equip Co, March- May 1947 (Box 9, Folder 73)
  - Pre-Shrunk Masonry Sales, May- June 1947 (Box 9, Folder 74)
  - Protection Products Mfg Co, June- July 1947 (Box 9, Folder 75)
  - Protexol Corp., March 1947 (Box 9, Folder 76)
  - Miscellaneous R, February- December 1947 (Box 9, Folder 77)
  - Radford Limestone Co., February- December 1947 (Box 9, Folder 78)
  - Rapid Transit Co, May- June 1947 (Box 9, Folder 79)
  - Rector and Fielder Electric Co, June- October 1947 (Box 9, Folder 80)
  - Arthur Reid, February- November 1947 (Box 9, Folder 81)
  - Red Jacket Coal Sales Co, January- November 1947 (Box 9, Folder 82)
  - Reidsville Printing Co, April 1947 (Box 9, Folder 83)
  - Research Institute of Amer, February- October 1947 (Box 9, Folder 84)
  - Revolution Cotton Mills, May- October 1947 (Box 9, Folder 85)
  - J. E. Rhoads and Sons, January- November 1947 (Box 9, Folder 86)
  - J W Ridenhour, January- February 1947 (Box 9, Folder 87)
  - Riverside Mills, January 1947 (Box 9, Folder 88)
  - Roanoke Concrete Products, January- June 1947 (Box 9, Folder 89)
  - Roanoke Engineering Sales, June- September 1947 (Box 9, Folder 90)
  - Roanoke Iron Works, June- November 1947 (Box 9, Folder 91)
  - Rock Hill Printing and Fin Co, March- September 1947 (Box 9, Folder 92)
  - R. G. Ross and Co, July- November 1947 (Box 9, Folder 93)
  - David Rothschild Co, April- May 1947 (Box 9, Folder 94)
  - Rutherford Freight Lines, January- April 1947 (Box 9, Folder 95)
  - Joseph J. Ryerson and Sons, February- May 1947 (Box 9, Folder 96)
  - Miscellaneous S, 1947 (Box 9, Folder 97)
  - Saco-Lowell Co, January 1947- January 1948 (Box 9, Folder 98)
  - Safeway Steel Scaffolds of Va, April 1947 (Box 9, Folder 99)
  - Salem Steel Co, February- July 1947 (Box 9, Folder 100)
  - Sanford Sash Co., February- March 1947 (Box 9, Folder 101)
  - Sanymetal Products Co, August- December 1947 (Box 9, Folder 102)
  - J W Scott and Co, March- August 1947 (Box 9, Folder 103)
  - Charles Schad Inc., March 1947 (Box 9, Folder 104)
  - Sears Roebuck ad Co, February- June 1947 (Box 9, Folder 105)
  - Security Life and Trust Co., 1947 (Box 9, Folder 106)
  - Service Appliance Co, February- October 1947 (Box 9, Folder 107)
  - Sherwin Williams Co., 1947 (Box 9, Folder 108)
  - J E Serrine and Co, April- June 1947 (Box 9, Folder 109)
  - S K F Industries, January- November 1947 (Box 9, Folder 110)
  - Slaughter Machinery Company, February- August 1947 (Box 9, Folder 111)
  - Smith-Courtney Company, October 1946- September 1947 (Box 9, Folder 112)
  - E E Smith and Son, March- April 1947 (Box 9, Folder 113)
  - Sonoco Products Co., March- September 1947 (Box 9, Folder 114)
  - Sacony-Vacuum Oil Co, April- December 1947 (Box 9, Folder 115)
  - Southeastern Paint and Decorating Co, May 1947 (Box 9, Folder 116)
  - Sou. Conference on Human Relations, 1947 (Box 9, Folder 117)
  - Southern Converting Co, January- November 1947 (Box 9, Folder 118)
  - Southern Electric Service Co, February- March 1947 (Box 9, Folder 119)
  - Southern Machinery and Supply Co., January 1947 (Box 9, Folder 120)
  - Southern Nail Co., August- October 1947 (Box 9, Folder 121)
  - Southern Oxygen Co., January- August 1947 (Box 9, Folder 122)
  - Spaugh Paper Co., January- November 1947 (Box 9, Folder 123)
  - Spindale Mills, Inc., June 1947 (Box 9, Folder 124)
  - A. E. Staley Mfg. Co., March- September 1947 (Box 9, Folder 125)
  - Standard Dupicating Machines, July 1947 (Box 9, Folder 126)
  - Standard Electric Time Co., August 1947 (Box 9, Folder 127)
  - Standard Oil Co. of N.J., February- October 1947 (Box 9, Folder 128)
  - Standard Pressed Steel Co., April- June 1947 (Box 9, Folder 129)
  - Steel Heddle Mfg. Co., 1947 (Box 9, Folder 130)
  - Stein Hall and Co., June- July 1947 (Box 9, Folder 131)
  - The Douglas T. Sterling Co., May- June 1947 (Box 9, Folder 132)
  - Stickle Steam Specialties, June- November 1947 (Box 9, Folder 133)
  - Gus Suckow, Jr., February- November 1947 (Box 9, Folder 134)
  - Sugar Beets Products Co., November 1946- June 1947 (Box 9, Folder 135)
  - Superior Sterling Co., 1947 (Box 9, Folder 136)
  - Dr. E C Sutphin, July- September 1947 (Box 9, Folder 137)
  - Swift and Co, May- December 1947 (Box 9, Folder 138)
  - Sykes, Inc., May- September 1947 (Box 9, Folder 139)
  - Miscellaneous T, January- October 1947 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Taylor Instrument, March- April 1947 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Terrell Machine Company, January- September 1947 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Textile Mill Supply Co., March- November 1947 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Textile Parts, Inc., January- June 1947 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Textile Specialty Co., January 1946- November 1947 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Tidewater Supply Co, April- November 1947 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - The Todd Co., Inc., February- September 1947 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Tompkins Label Service, February- May 1947 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Traffic Dept. (folder 1 of 3), 1947 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Traffic Dept. (folder 2 of 3), 1947 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Traffic Dept. (folder 3 of 3), 1947 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Trinacria Specialty Mfg. Co., January- April 1947 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Tristate Electrical Supply Co., July- November 1947 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Truitt Mfg Co, 1947 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Miscellaneous U, March- December 1947 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - U.S Govt. C.P.A. -- J.H.A. -- W.A.A., December 1946- March 1947 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - U.S. Govt. Federal Power Commission, December 1946- December 1947 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - U.S. Govt. Social Security and Treasury, February- November 1947 (Box 155, Folder 11)
  - Factory Ins. (C.L. Hildreth), May- December 1949 (Box 155, Folder 12)
  - The First National Bank, April- May 1949 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - J. Cam Fields (Fields Mfg. Co), February- September 1949 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Flowers School Equipment Co., October- December 1949 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Fries, Town of, March- November 1949 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Miscellaneous G, 1949 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Gates Rubber Co, March- November 1949 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - General Electric Supply, January- October 1949 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - General Motor Lines, 1949 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Giant Mfg. Co (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Golden's Foundry and Machine Co, September 1949 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Gossett Machine Works, January 1949 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Graham Mfg Co, March 1949 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Graton and Knight Co, January 1949 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Grayson County, July 1949 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Greensboro Loom Reed Co, February- December 1949 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Hobert N. Grubb, 1949 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Guideposts, January 1949 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - The Edwin J. Guth Co, July 1949 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Miscellaneous H, September 1948- December 1949 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - H and B American Machine Co, January 1949 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - H and P Spool and Bobbin, April- May 1949 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Mrs W G Hamner, May 1949 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - The Hampshire Corporation, March- August 1949 (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - N. B. Handy Co, February- April 1949 (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Hartmann Sanders Co, March- October 1949 (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - William H. Heagerty, January 1949 (Box 10, Folder 46)